ranc



PROFILE

I am an Embedded Software Engineer with +4 years of experience in SW embedded systems and HW validation.

I consider myself as a person with initiative, adaptability and responsible.

I am interested in deepening my professional career in software embedded development.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+34 661 36 02 77

WEBSITE:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marcoan tonio-perez/

EMAIL:

marcoperezag1@gmail.com

LOCATION:

Barcelona, Spain

LANGUAGES

Spanish (native) English (professional) Catalan (professional)

MARCO A. PEREZ GUEVARA

EMBEDDED SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EDUCATION

Universitat Ramon Llull, Barcelona, Spain

2016 - 2021

Electronic Engineer of Telecommunications

UNEFA, Aragua, Venezuela

2012 - 2016

Electronic Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Thermo King – Embedded Software Engineer

July 2021 – Now, Spain

Currently, developing embedded system coding in Python for testing automation tool. Plus, leading hardware definition in new microprocessor validation for power electronics.

Universitat Ramon Llull – Embedded Systems Lecturer

September 2019 – July 2021, Spain

Defined and designed projects using embedded systems coding in C++ and Python under Linux, Windows, and Microchip PIC architecture.

Hewlett Packard – Embedded Systems Engineer

May 2016 - March 2018, Spain

Developed test suite using Linux embedded system coding in C++ for hardware testing.

BAS Projects – Embedded Systems Engineer

May 2014 - March 2016, Venezuela

Developed data acquisition using embedded system coding in C for energy saving project.

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

Programming Languages such as C++, C, and Python.

Embedded Systems.

Windows and Linux as Operative Systems.

Software and Hardware Validation.

CI/CD.

Qt, Yocto, Git experience.

Repository and Agile Methodology.